# Branden Daniel Ng

Front-End Web Developer Melbourne, VIC

linkedin.com/in/brandendaniel in

github.com/BrandenDaniel 😯

Web Portfolio - branden.vercel.app

**J** 04 32 375 587

Experienced front-end web developer with a fiery passion for transforming static wireframes into interactive, beautiful spaced websites. Throughout my journey, I've had the privilege to collaborate with a diverse range of clients and businesses. I am currently learning React.js and API integrations.

## **Work Experience**

### LeasePLUS Group - SafeCode

Sept. 2022 - Present Melbourne CBD, VIC

Front-end Web Developer

SafeCode, a LeasePLUS subsidiary, creates novated leasing and salary packaging interfaces for individuals and businesses. With 100,000+ users, they cater to diverse clients across Australia.

Worked on proprietary leasing/salary packaging software for LeasePlus Group

• Management of all LeasePlus group's websites/portals (over 5+)

### LeasePLUS Group - SalaryPackagingPLUS

Accounts Officer - salary deductions receivable & payable

Apr. 2022 - Sept. 2022 Melbourne CBD, VIC

# Arcadian Digital &

#### Junior Front-end Web Developer

Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020 Melbourne CBD. VIC

As a bespoke digital and marketing agency, Arcadian deliver tailored solutions to organisations of all sizes. I worked with extremely talented engineers during my time there.

- · Collaborative work with project managers and lead/senior developers
- · Build and structure WordPress child themes
- · Build and maintian company's own WordPress plugins and themes

#### Bebble Media &

**Tech Stack & Skills** 

May. 2018 — Jun. 2019

North Laverton, VIC

# Junior Front-end Web Developer

A small digital agency in West Melbourne with in-house designers and developers. Specialising in WordPress, they assist small business owners in expanding their ecommerce and online presence.

- · Collaborate with web/graphic designers to reach mockup standards
- Integrations of plugins + customisation of plugins to suit client's specifics
- Manipulation of software styles (i.e plugins, themes) exact to design mockups

HTML JavaScript CSS Sass React  jQuery Bootstrap Git Azure deployment		ETFs & Index Funds Personal Finance Tech  Critically Acclaimed Films Youtube	
Work/Projects			
My Web Portfolio ♥ React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS (Sass)	2023	MySalPack (employee portal) <i>&amp;</i> JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap	2023
MySalPack (employer portal) <i>§</i> JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Blazor, Bootstrap	2022	Jalna <i>∲</i> PHP (WordPress), Sass, jQuery	2019
Spinach <i>№</i> PHP (WordPress), Sass, jQuery	2019	Kader Boot Co. <i></i> CSS, HTML, jQuery	2018

Interests & Hobbies

### **Education**

Udacity Front End Web Developer Nanodegree

Online Oct. 2017 - May 2018

**Team Treehouse** 

Online

Front End Web Development Track

May - Aug. 2017

Melbourne, VIC Jul. 2016 - Apr. 2017

**RMIT University** 

Completed 48 credits towards a Bachelor of Information Technology

# Relevant Courses Included:

- Web Programming
- · User-centered Design